playmo.my 2011-01-14

# PLAYMO - Privacy Policy

PlayMo strongly believes that you have the right to control the use of your personally identifiable information, and is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. We value your trust and want you to understand how we protect, collect, use and disclose the personally identifiable information you share with us. 

This privacy statement applies to personally identifiable information we obtain anytime you interact with PlayMo such as when you visit our website ([playmo.my](http://www.playmo.my/)), participate in the PlayMo contest or contact PlayMo support, both online and offline. 

These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personally identifiable information you provide will be used. 

**What We Collect**

PlayMo collects personally identifiable information in order to create or enhance our relationship with you. The information you provide is used to fulfil your specific request. The type of personally identifiable information we collect when using the PlayMo Service may include (but not limited to) contact information such as: 

  * First and last name

  * Mobile number

  * Email address

  * Billing information

When we collect personally identifiable information from you it is because you are voluntarily submitting the information to us when you:

  * Register on our website(s) to obtain downloadable mobile entertainment content, such as ringtones, games, graphics, videos and/or other information data

  * Sign up for one-time downloads or subscriptions via SMS using your mobile phone, or

  * Participate in activities like contests, games, surveys, forums, in connection with content or suggestions you submit to us, or chats or bulletin boards.

We may also obtain personally identifiable information from reputable third parties and sources including public databases.

**How We Use the Information We Gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: 

  * Complete your transaction

  * Alleviate any problems that may arise in effecting the transaction, 

  * To better understand and manage our ongoing relationship with you

  * To assure good service

  * To prevent fraud and abuse

  * For purposes of verification and risk management and otherwise with consent or as permitted or required by law. 

PlayMo may store personally identifiable information on databases for the purposes of the administration of our business, including our ongoing relationship with you, for market research and, only with your consent, for direct marketing purposes. As permitted by applicable law, we may merge personally identifiable information with public information or other information received from reputable vendors to update contact information or to enhance demographic profiles. 

How We Share Your Personally Identifiable Information  
PlayMo may share your personally identifiable information with companies that are affiliated with us that are part of PlayMo. Provided you have given us permission, PlayMo may share your personally identifiable information with advertisers and business partners that are not affiliated with PlayMo, but would like to send you information about their products and services. However, you will always have the opportunity to instruct us not to share your information with unaffiliated third parties when personally identifiable information is collected. 

PlayMo employees, agents and contractors must have a legitimate business reason to obtain access to your personally identifiable information. PlayMo may share your personally identifiable information with outside contractors or agents who help manage our information activities (i.e., administration, order fulfillment, statistical analyses), but they may only use your personally identifiable information to provide PlayMo with a specific service and not for any other purpose. 

PlayMo may also enter into agreements with outside companies that possess the technology that allows PlayMo to customize the advertising and marketing messages you receive on PlayMo's website(s). Your non-personally identifiable information and click stream data about your activities on PlayMo's website(s) may be shared with these companies so this customization can be accomplished. These companies will not share your information with any third party or use it for any other purpose. Anonymous click stream and demographic information may also be shared with PlayMo’s advertisers and business partners. Such information may include: 

  * Visitors’ IP address

  * Browser type

  * Date, time and duration of visit

  * Particular pages viewed

These third parties are authorized to use your personally identifiable information only as necessary to provide these services to us. 

We may also disclose your personally identifiable information:

  * As required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process 

  * When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud or respond to a written government request 

  * For the purposes of processing requested transactions or to perform business support functions on our behalf

  * If PlayMo becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personally identifiable information becomes subject to a different privacy statement 

  * To any other third party with your prior consent to do so 

We will share your personally identifiable information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Statement. We do not otherwise sell, rent, trade or share your personal identifiable information to third parties for their promotional purposes.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual.

The site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personally identifiable information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You may encounter cookies from third parties when using the PlayMo services on websites that we do not control (for example, if you view a web page created by a third party or use an application developed by a third party, there may be a cookie placed by that web page or application.)

PlayMo does not control these cookies and visitors to our website(s) should check the privacy policy of the advertiser to see how it uses cookies.

PlayMo may use cookies and similar tools to relate your use of our website(s) to personally identifiable information obtained from you or a reputable third party. For example, if you've asked us to send you information about our upcoming products or promotions, cookie and/or click stream data about your activities on PlayMo website(s) may allow us to limit the materials we provide you to items we think you will find interesting, based on your prior online activities and preferences. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may however prevent you from taking full advantage of the Site, such as your subscription option page.

**Choice and Opt Out**

PlayMo will not use or share your personally identifiable information in ways incompatible with the ones described above without providing you a choice. You mustopt-out of any sharing of personally identifiable information you have authorized or consented to as described above. However, to the extent that applicable law requires express consent or “opt-in” for the collection and use of personal information, PlayMo will maintain processes and procedures to ensure such information is collected with express consent. Personally identifiable information will not be used to directly market PlayMo services unless that possible use of the information has been disclosed and a choice provided. 

Commitment to Data Security  
Ensuring your information is secured is a priority for PlayMo and your personally identifiable information is kept secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. PlayMo agents are bound by appropriate data safeguarding obligations. 

Access to personally identifiable information is restricted to employees and service providers who need to have access to that information as described in this privacy statement. PlayMo requires its service providers to observe standards with respect to the security, collection, use and sharing of personally identifiable information, and to comply with applicable law. We make reasonable efforts to ensure security on our systems.

In the event of a security breach, we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate action. By using the PlayMo service, you agree that PlayMo may communicate with you electronically or via short messaging service (SMS).

**Use by Children**

PlayMo will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 18, without the consent of a parent or guardian. If a child under 18 submits personal information and we learn the personal information is the information of a child under 18, we will attempt to delete the information as soon as possible. 

**Changes in this Privacy Statement**

PlayMo believes your trust is paramount to us and will ensure that its privacy practices are constantly reviewed. 

If we decide to change our privacy practices, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about the online privacy statement for this site or its implementation you may email us at [myhelp@tap.com.sg](mailto:myhelp@tap.com.sg) or contact us at 0327727395 (local rate) from Mondays to Fridays, 9am to 6pm. Alternatively, we can be contacted by mail at the following address: 

26A Temple Street  
Singapore 058571
